

### **Contacts**

a.bertash.dev@gmail.com

@AndrewBertash

github.com/ABertashDev

+38 096 728 37 24

Rivne, Ukraine

## Skills

.NET 6, C#

ASP .NET Core **EF** Core

LINQ

Razor Pages

Web API

**MVC** 

Swagger

PostMan

nUnit

HTML/CSS XML/JSON 1C Enterprise MS SQL Server MySQL, T-SQL PostgreSQL Apache

**TeamCity** 

Jira/Confluence

 $\bigcirc\bigcirc$ P

**REST API** SOLID, GOF

Agile, Scrum,

other software

development

methodologies

## Languages

English B1 (Intermediate) Ukrainian Native Russian Fluent

# Andrii Bertash

#### JUNIOR .NET SOFTWARE ENGINEER

## **Profile**

I am a software engineer with more than 6 years of commercial experience. I have organizational and problem-solving skills with a high level of self-motivation for work. I am easy and fast learn new technologies, frameworks, tools, etc.

I am an adaptable person. I have worked with different customers. They had disparate requirements and expectations of me. I have been able to adjust my possibilities and skills to meet each of their needs.

I am good at producing quality work in a team environment. In addition, I am very comfortable with public speaking.

Seeking to apply my experience and skills to benefit your company as a .NET developer. I am tired to be unrecognized developer and it is a reason why I want to switch to .NET technologies stack and become a part of the "true developers" community

# **Projects**

Junior .NET

Online recipe book

**GitHub** 

01.2023 - now

Online recipe book. ASP .NET Core, Web API, EF Core, LINQ, mySQL, HTML/CSS

## Experience

1C Developer / Architect / PM / QA

03.2021 - now

Freelance projects, Rivne

Participated in many projects on the development and implementation 1C/BAS solutions for various types of businesses. Agreement work with the customers. Analysis and description of requirements. Connection trading equipment. Technical support

1C Developer / Architect / QA

08.2019 - now

ERP Data Service Ltd., Rivne

Franchisee team member. Development of solutions for automation of business processes and API integrations. Analysis and description of requirements. Connection of trading equipment

1C Developer

06.2016 - 07.2019

Renome-Smart Ltd., Rivne

Franchisee team member. Participated in many projects on the development and implementation of ERP and CRM systems based on 1C for various types of businesses. API integrations

Teacher/lecturer 05.2014 - 05.2016

GRAND (itosvita), Rivne

Teaching children according to the program, explanation of the material, checking the completion of tasks, maintaining documentation

# **Education**

Junior .NET

**EPAM University** 

SoftServe Academy

Certificate

Certificate

06.2022 - 10.2022

**BAS: Professional** 

Successfully completed .NET Summer Program 2022

HS "SAB"

Professional in the implementation of BAS solutions for business

automation

Trainee QA

09.2018 - 10.2018

Course "Test automation with Python"

1C: Professional

1C Ukraine

Certificate

Diploma

09.2017

03 2021

Professional in using 1C: Enterprise 8.3 platform mechanisms

Bachelor's Degree 09.2013 - 07.2017

Rivne State University of the Humanities

Economic Cybernetics Bachelor's Degree (Diploma with honours)